https://www.southview.org/privacy-policy

Southview Community Church maintains this website as a service to its attenders and visitors. The Privacy Policy and Terms of Use set forth below govern your use of this website, and by using the website you agree to be bound by them. Therefore, please read the Privacy Policy and Terms of Use carefully before you use this website. If you do not agree with our Privacy Policy and Terms of Use, please do not use this website.PRIVACY POLICYLog FilesLike most websites, this website logs your IP address, browser type, hits on particular pages, and other general traffic information. This information is not linked to personally identifiable information and you remain anonymous.Use of Personal InformationIf you give us personal information, including for purposes of submitting a testimony, signing up for a newsletter, contacting the church, or posting or commenting on a blog, we will not share that information with any third party, except to the extent necessary to complete transactions or if we believe that it is appropriate to share such information in order to comply with the law, to enforce or apply the Privacy Policy or Terms of Use, or to protect the rights, property, or safety of the website, any user of the site, Southview Community Church, or any of its staff, officers, employees, agents, or affiliated organizations.Posting of Personal InformationPlease be aware that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online - for example, in a posted testimony, on a message board, or through email - that information can be collected and used by others. By disclosing personal information online, you may make that information available to others who could use it to send you unsolicited messages or for other purposes you may not desire or intend.Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA)While our website is not subject to COPPA, we love children and understand that it is very important to maintain their privacy. Therefore, our policy is that we will not knowingly collect, use, or distribute to third parties any personally identifiable information from any child under 13 years old without verifiable parental consent and not knowingly allow any child under 13 years old to publicly post or distribute personally identifiable information without verifiable parental consent.TERMS OF USETrademarks and Copyrights; All Rights ReservedSouthview Community Church reserves all of its rights under and does not grant any express or implied rights to you or any other user of the website under any trademark, copyright, trade secret, or other intellectual property law, except as provided below with regard to the use of downloaded messages. This website and all of the text, graphics, pictures, audio messages, video materials, downloadable materials, and all other materials and content on the website are copyrighted by and are the property of Southview Community Church. You may not use them in any manner without the express written consent of Southview Community Church.Use of Downloaded MessagesWe are glad to make our sermons and other messages available for download free of charge. However, your right to use downloaded messages is limited. A message downloaded from our website is only for personal use, and can only be used on the computer or other device onto which it was downloaded and cannot be duplicated or distributed in any way. If you would like to share one of our messages with a friend, you can either have your friend download the message from our website or request or pick up a CD of the message from Ministry Central to give to your friend.Disclaimer of WarrantiesAll materials and other content of this website or accessible from this website are provided on an "as is" basis and Southview Community Church expressly disclaims any express or implied warranties or conditions of any kind, including without limitation any warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose or use, title, or non-infringement.Limitation of LiabilityBy using this website you agree that Southview Community Church and each of its staff, officers, employees, other agents, and affiliated organizations shall not be liable to you for any damage of any kind arising from or related to the use of this website or any website for which a link is provided on this site.Applicable LawUse of this website and any claim or dispute arising from or related to use of this website is governed by the laws of the State of Virginia, without regard to any rule or principle regarding conflicts of laws. The exclusive jurisdiction and venue of any such claim or dispute shall be in the state and federal courts for Fairfax County, Virginia.
